Hello everyone, how are you all?  My name is
Ashish and you are watching Grow with Ashish
Bro.  In this video I am going to
inform you about the hiring which is coming
from one of the most famous
insurance company named ICICI LB
which is hiring you on multiple
location and multiple profile which is a
payroll job.  So don't miss it.   Please
watch the video completely because
I keep bringing such non-BPO jobs with payroll jobs.
So please subscribe to our channel.
We have an Instagram page with the same name.
So you can follow me there also.
So go there and you will
find the link in bio.  Follow me.  So without further
delay let's get started on the video.
Yes sir.  So how are you guys?
As I told you in the video, the proper thing is that
ICICI LB General Insurance is hiring,
which is quick insurance, age
insurance, motor insurance, all these
are provided.  Ok?  So this
is a payroll job.  There are no BPO jobs.  This is a
total non BPPO and payroll based job.
Your salary will come in the name of ICICI.  The ICIC
ID card will be yours.  Ok?  So proper
pay roll job.
I will tell you the complete difference between payroll and non-payroll in some next
video.  Further we move
towards our hiring information which will be
our job role.  Job Roles They Are Hiring.
Three to four is their job role
designation.  Like the first customer
service associate with two things inside.
Both email process and calling process will remain.
And the second one will be of their sales manager.
is of Relationship Manager and is of
Sales Associate.  For all three
they need 6 months experience plus
graduation.  Not for these three but for all of them
because in any Pel job, there is a very
rare chance that you will get
eligibility even in undergraduate.  Ok?  But
graduation is required in this.  At least graduation is
required.  Graduation plus fresher and graduate
plus experience both are eligible in this.
Ok?  The only thing is that
you will not be able to go to Sales Associate.
They need 6 months experience in Sales Associate.  Ok
?  Here is its job role.
I have mentioned the eligibility.  Also, you will have to be a graduate and provide experience in the
role in which they require experience.
Ok?   The
rest of the locations which will be there in this, the ones
which are currently hiring, right now your Vashi
location is being done in Mumbai, Navi Mumbai is being done
, Pune is being done and Indore is being done.
These four locations, brother, their hiring
is open right now.  At present it has been closed in Gurgaon also.
So soon they will open in NCR also.  It is
coming and as soon as it comes in NCR,
I will update you through my Instagram by
making a short video and
if you have not followed the channel, I will
request our Instagram page, the
link is in the bio, there is a page with the same name,
you can probably search Grow with
Ashish Br, you can follow it
for short and quick updates, I keep
giving there, let's move towards my video,
so let me tell you what will be the work type in it,
like if suppose
you are selected in Customer Service Associate, then a
calling inbound call
comes, like if I am a customer,
I called, yes sir, I
need a claim, I want to cancel the policy.   If
I need a policy, you guys will handle it.
Ok?  So it became about calling.
As these calls come in,
customers will keep asking similar queries.  Well, you have to
resolve.  Ok?  Father, who is your
sales associate or relationship manager.
Relationship Manager's position remains the same.  It's just one
step above that, one step above these callings.
Yes, they have to sell their policies.
Because Sales' Relationship
Manager and Sales Associate.  In Sales Associate,
you have to do the same outban calling.  You
will get a lead.  Lead generation work is involved in it.
Leads will be generated.  You have to call him and say,
yes sir, you had seen the insurance, you have to
convince him about something like this.  So in this
profile candidate must have strong
communication skills and convincing
power.  So both should come.  One should know how to convince
and should also have skills.
Earning for both Hindi and English.  And further I would like to
tell you about the benefits.  But as a benefit,
you are given corporate insurance which
you get in every corporate.
You will also get Save Corporate Insurance.  And there
is five days working, many companies are
still doing six days working.  But
in this you get five days working.
You will not feel that much pressure.  and there
is shift and fixed day shift.  You may be a girl
, a boy, or anyone.  Ok?  So
you will get day shift.  The shifts in this will be
9:30 to 6:30 and 10:30 to 7:30, both these
shifts run in it.  So both these shifts will be
for you.  There
is no other shift apart from this.  There is a very good option for daily shift
in Indore.
And if I
talk about the salary, then the salary that you get in this,
because suppose you go as a fresher, then
if you go as a fresher, then
you get a salary up to 2.5 LPA and if you have experience
of customer calling, then maximum,
I think, it is going up to 2.9 LPA and
more will come in sales.  If
you get incentives in sales, your salary
can go up to Rs 4 LPA.  Ok?
I am telling you about all four locations.  If you are hiring at all four locations, then the
salary at all four locations will remain the same.  4 LPA maximum plus
incentives for maximum sales.  So these
are the three salary structures.  Sir, this is the
second interview round of ICICI General Insurance, there will be
two interview rounds in it.  No one is
more than no test.  There
is no MCAT.  There is no problem brother.  The amount of
Mcut or percentage does all this.  Nothing
simple HR round interview round sorry
operation manager's round.  Brother, HR will
ask you questions.  He will ask about the intro, he will
ask about the office.  If you are a fresher, he will ask about the city.
Why do you want to do it?  ICC long job
will ask some such questions.  Rest of the experience is there, he will
ask about that experience.  There is nothing more than this.
And regarding operations etc. also he
asks the same question that what did you do in the company
?  He used to do it, take calls, how many calls did he
take, what did he do?  Just everything means
very simple round, I think
science will be in long because there are not many rounds,
only two rounds.  Your job will be included in this in two rounds.
Ok?  The rest of the
process is because it is an on-roll job.  There
is no process in this.  It is a
process in itself.  If you want to know the LOB on the process name then
I told you that it will be for
calling, inbound calling and
sales and there is the profile of relationship manager.
So there are three profiles.  And let me
tell you about the age limit, the
maximum age limit in this is 30.
By the way, take out 28 as the maximum age,
in this the age criteria will be accepted only till 30.
Ok?  I will
confirm the rest and you will get that confirmed information
in the description.  Whatever is
written in the description will remain confirmed.
Ok?  So I will give you the confirmation and complete
information in the description also.   Make
sure you check the description.  If I
forget something here,
you will find it in the description and if it is not in the description,
please comment so
that I can know.  Yes, if I have
n't told you then I will tell you in the comments.
Ok?  Don't mind.  And if you
talk about growth,
if I talk about growth and development, look, it is a pale job, then
obviously you will get growth and name, there is a
little bit of reputation that yes I am
working in Lobert, even not rather than BPPO, I am
not working in BPO, I am
working in a long, it is a pale job, so there is a little bit of growth,
your chances of growth are also
good, after one year you
can fill IGP, sorry guys for
interrupting between the video, but I
forgot to tell one thing because HR reference
is available and if you want to apply, then
you can directly contact on the HR number, there are
different HR for different locations.  So if you
want to apply then you can DM me and
you can also get the HR contact number from me.
So I will give you the HR contact number.
So you can apply by sending a direct message.  You
can go for direct interview.  So now you can enjoy the
complete video.  You will get all the information
in the description.  So this
is the video that I told you about and before this
I had already uploaded a video.  If you
go and see, it is a job in ICICI Bank
or ICICI Insurance.  So both are
jobs of ICICI only.  So go and watch this
video quickly and like this video.
Don't forget to subscribe to the channel and press the bell icon because before that, if you
also watch the video, it will reach you first,
so press the bell icon and turn it on so that
you get the notification
of my video first. Rest, if you still have a query, concern regarding
hire in or the
job role, as well, then you can drop a comment
and you can also contact us on Instagram
and twitter, as well, this is all from my
side, thank you so much for watching the
video, have a good day, thank you, that's all for today, for now, like
you, I am also disappointed,
but the world is based on hope. The heart is sad and
betrayed, but it is not broken and I have not lost hope.